[
    {
        "Question": "zenith",
        "Answer": "peak",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "seek",
        "Answer": "attempt",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "environment",
        "Answer": "setting",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "appraisal",
        "Answer": "evaluation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "subjected to",
        "Answer": "exposed to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "redundancy",
        "Answer": "duplication",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "aware of",
        "Answer": "familiar with",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ratio",
        "Answer": "proportion",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "endowing",
        "Answer": "providing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "efforts",
        "Answer": "attempts",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "strictly",
        "Answer": "exclusively",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "periodically",
        "Answer": "regularly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "concealed",
        "Answer": "hidden",
        "Options": "covered"
    },
    {
        "Question": "fuels",
        "Answer": "provides energy  for",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "criticize",
        "Answer": "debate",
        "Options": "find fault"
    },
    {
        "Question": "ritual",
        "Answer": "ceremonial",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "identifiable",
        "Answer": "recognizable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ambivalent",
        "Answer": "mixed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "declining",
        "Answer": "weakening",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "keenly",
        "Answer": "deeply",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "decisive",
        "Answer": "determining",
        "Options": "definite"
    },
    {
        "Question": "decide",
        "Answer": "determine",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "complaint",
        "Answer": "protest",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "related",
        "Answer": "connected",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "illuminates",
        "Answer": "lights",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exude",
        "Answer": "give off",
        "Options": "release"
    },
    {
        "Question": "guarantee",
        "Answer": "ensure",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "asset",
        "Answer": "advantage",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "readily",
        "Answer": "easily",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cue",
        "Answer": "hint",
        "Options": "clue"
    },
    {
        "Question": "chronic",
        "Answer": "inveterate",
        "Options": "habitual/ persistent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "expansive",
        "Answer": "large",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enthusiasitc",
        "Answer": "eager",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "countervail",
        "Answer": "oppose",
        "Options": "compensate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "gifted",
        "Answer": "talented",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "stagnation",
        "Answer": "lack of growth",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "endeavors",
        "Answer": "efforts",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "curious",
        "Answer": "strange",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "confront",
        "Answer": "face",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "tangled",
        "Answer": "twisted together",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "allocation",
        "Answer": "distribution",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "disorder",
        "Answer": "anarchy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pervasive",
        "Answer": "widespread",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "admit",
        "Answer": "let in",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "attachment to",
        "Answer": "preference to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "boom",
        "Answer": "expansion",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pursue",
        "Answer": "practice",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "abstract",
        "Answer": "not concrete",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "disentangle",
        "Answer": "disband",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "potential",
        "Answer": "possible",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "traditionally",
        "Answer": "originally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "homogenous",
        "Answer": "uniform",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dissipate",
        "Answer": "disperse",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "verging",
        "Answer": "bordering",
        "Options": "confirming"
    },
    {
        "Question": "status",
        "Answer": "importance",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "adept",
        "Answer": "skillful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "complex",
        "Answer": "elaborate/ complicated",
        "Options": "system/ made things more difficult"
    },
    {
        "Question": "chaotic",
        "Answer": "disorganized",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "first rank",
        "Answer": "highest quality",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "counterpart",
        "Answer": "equivalent",
        "Options": "similitude"
    },
    {
        "Question": "era",
        "Answer": "period",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "contends",
        "Answer": "argues",
        "Options": "dispute"
    },
    {
        "Question": "congestion",
        "Answer": "overcrowding",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "devour",
        "Answer": "eat",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "extracted",
        "Answer": "removed",
        "Options": "taken out of"
    },
    {
        "Question": "outlying",
        "Answer": "far from the center",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "article",
        "Answer": "item/ object",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "alliances",
        "Answer": "partnerships",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mortality",
        "Answer": "death",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deter ",
        "Answer": "stop",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "attendant",
        "Answer": "accompanying",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "consistent",
        "Answer": "uniform",
        "Options": "regular"
    },
    {
        "Question": "swift",
        "Answer": "fast",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "indiscriminate",
        "Answer": "random",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inclination",
        "Answer": "preferences",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "underestimate",
        "Answer": "underrate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "plausible",
        "Answer": "believable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cope",
        "Answer": "adapt/ deal with",
        "Options": "manage/ handle"
    },
    {
        "Question": "provided that",
        "Answer": "as long as",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "suitable",
        "Answer": "appropriate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "appreciated",
        "Answer": "approved",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "chisel",
        "Answer": "carve",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "discrete",
        "Answer": "separate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "architecture",
        "Answer": "structure",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "abundant",
        "Answer": "plentiful/ substantial",
        "Options": "ample/ affluent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "elevate",
        "Answer": "raise",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "puncture",
        "Answer": "pierce",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "absurd",
        "Answer": "ridiculous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "painstakingly",
        "Answer": "with great effort",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "expediency",
        "Answer": "advantage",
        "Options": "convenience"
    },
    {
        "Question": "twenty or so",
        "Answer": "roughly twenty",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "promote",
        "Answer": "encourage",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "gains",
        "Answer": "increases",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "flourished",
        "Answer": "prospered",
        "Options": "succeed"
    },
    {
        "Question": "agile",
        "Answer": "astute/ quick and active",
        "Options": "clever"
    },
    {
        "Question": "prolonged",
        "Answer": "extended",
        "Options": "lengthy"
    },
    {
        "Question": "pointed out",
        "Answer": "stated",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "meager",
        "Answer": "very low",
        "Options": "thin"
    },
    {
        "Question": "intergrated",
        "Answer": "combined",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "oversaw",
        "Answer": "supervised",
        "Options": ""
    }
]